

OLEKSANDR PANCHELIUGA

FRONT END / WEBUI DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm an ambitious student aimed at getting my first experience at your company. I would like to continue to learn and become a more knowledgeable and skilled Front End Developer.

I am really passionate about IT and now I feel I'm ready for teamwork.

SKILLS

- Version Management
 - Git, GitHub
- Dynamic stylesheet
 - sass/scss
- IDE/Editors
 - WebStorm, VS Code
- Package management and tasks runners
 - Npm, Gulp, Webpack
- Programming Languages / Technologies
 - JavaScript, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3
- DB
 - MongoDB, MySQL
- Frameworks, Libraries
 - ReactJS, Express.js, Twitter Bootstrap

WORK EXPERIENCE

CEO. CO-FOUNDER

Geoinform Service PE, Korets, Ukraine | 2009 - Present

- Developing responsive and market-driven company
- Managing relationships with key stakeholders
- Directing land management design and development
- Advising customers regarding land legislation
- Conducting problem solving and troubleshooting

LAND SURVEYOR ENGINEER

Expert-Rivne-Land PE, Rivne, Ukraine | 2007 - 2009

- Developing and implementing land management projects
- Performing surveyor works

OTHER SKILLS

- · Excitement for learning
- Team player
- Ability to communicate effectively
- Adaptability
- · Attention to detail
- Good time management skills

GET IN CONTACT

- +38 097 645 01 74
- pancheliuga.o@gmail.com
- github.com/pancheliuga
- linkedin.com/in/pancheliuga
- Rivne, Ukraine

EDUCATION HISTORY

IT STEP ACADEMY

Rivne, Ukraine

Front End Developer | 2018 - Present

THE NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF WATER AND ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERING

Rivne, Ukraine

Land management and cadastre engineer | 2012 - 2013

THE NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF WATER AND ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERING

Rivne, Ukraine

Geographic information systems and technologies engineer | 2003 - 2008